How on earth did we come to this?
我们究竟是怎么落到这步田地的？
We protect our children obsessively from every harm; we scrutinize every carer, teacher or doctor with whom they come into contact.
我们近乎偏执地保护孩子免受一切伤害；凡是与孩子接触的看护人、老师或医生，我们都要逐一仔细审查。
Yet despite all this, one group, which in no way has their best interests at heart, has almost unconstrained access.
然而，尽管我们做了这一切，却有一个群体几乎可以不受约束地接触孩子，而这个群体根本就不是真心为孩子着想。
We seem to take it for granted that advertisers and marketers are allowed to condition even the youngest children.
我们似乎想当然地认为，广告商和营销人员可以去驯化哪怕是年纪最小的孩子。
Before children have even developed a proper sense of their own identity, or learned to handle money, they’re encouraged to associate status and self-worth with stuff, and to look to external things such as fame and wealth for validation.
孩子们甚至还没有形成应有的自我认同感，也还没学会管钱，就被鼓励把地位和自我价值与物质的东西联系起来，并指望从名气、财富等外在事物中获得认可。
We’re turning out little consumers rather than young citizens who will value themselves for what they contribute to the society in which they live.
我们正在培养的是一个个小消费者，而不是因自己对所在社会的贡献而看重自身价值的年轻公民。
We’ve reached this point so gradually that many of us have never questioned it.
我们是一点一点走到今天这一步的，这个过程如此缓慢，以至于我们当中很多人从未质疑过这种状况。
It’s crept up on us in the 60 years since advertisers started to target the young and found that they could recruit them to a commercial assault on their parents.
60年前，广告商开始把目标对准孩子，并发现可以拉拢他们加入针对父母的商业攻势；从那时起，这种状况就在我们不知不觉间逐渐形成了。
We’ve come to know it as “pester power”, or the ability of children to pressure parents to make certain purchases.
我们渐渐把它称作“纠缠力”，即孩子向父母施压、要他们购买某些东西的能力。
Many psychologists, child development experts and educators point to research suggesting that this emerging cradle-to-grave consumerism is contributing to growing rates of low self-esteem, depression and other forms of mental illness.
许多心理学家、儿童发展专家和教育工作者援引的研究表明，这种新兴的、从摇篮到坟墓的消费主义，正在助推自卑、抑郁和其他形式的精神疾病发病率不断上升。
Not all psychologists agree.
并非所有心理学家都认同这一点。
There’re plenty working hand in glove with a £12bn-a-year industry that has turned the manipulation of adult emotions and desires into an art form—often literally.
有很多心理学家与一个年产值达120亿英镑的产业紧密勾结，这个产业已经把操纵成年人的情感和欲望变成了一种艺术形式——而且往往就是字面意义上的艺术。
It’s also one that’s forever developing new ways to persuade our children to desire material possessions, and because of advertisements’ viral effect they only need to infect a few to reach the many.
这个产业还在不停地开发新手段，劝诱我们的孩子去渴求物质财富；而且由于广告具有病毒式传播效应，只需感染少数人，就能触及多数人。
Advertising and marketing can serve a useful purpose for children.
广告和营销可以对孩子起到有益的作用。
Marketing may help socialize children as consumers, inform them about products, and help them carve out unique identities as they reach adulthood.
营销或许能帮助孩子作为消费者实现社会化，让他们了解产品，并帮助他们在步入成年时打造出独特的自我认同。
Then, should we ban all advertising aimed at young children?
那么，我们是否应该禁止一切针对年幼儿童的广告呢？
I say yes.
我的回答是：应该。
Of course there’ll be plenty of objections to an outright ban on advertising to the under-11s.
当然，对于全面禁止面向11岁以下儿童的广告，会有很多反对意见。
There’ll be those who argue that would be a breach of freedom of speech and infringe the rights of corporations to brainwash little children into demanding their products.
会有人争辩说，这样做会破坏言论自由，并侵犯企业给小孩子洗脑、让他们吵着要买自家产品的权利。
Most parents hate what advertising does to their children, but we do have the power to end it and let our children grow up free from many of the pressures of consumerism until they’re old enough to make their own decisions.
大多数父母都痛恨广告给孩子造成的影响，但我们确实有能力终结这一切，让孩子在成长过程中摆脱消费主义带来的诸多压力，直到他们长大到能够自己做决定为止。
And though advertising is only part of an all-pervasive marketing culture, we need to make a start somewhere.
而且，在无处不在的营销文化中，广告虽然只是一部分，但我们总得从某个地方着手。
Let’s ban all advertising targeting children of primary school age and younger now.
让我们现在就禁止一切针对小学及学龄前儿童的广告吧。